How do you like your life? Um, not the
best one, but you know, it was a pretty
good one. Yeah, we had we had we had
some controversy out there, you know,
that putt doesn't count for a birdie,
another missed putt later somehow is now
a gimme with a birdie. That's all right,
you know, all in all in good fun.
You were up here, is that okay? Like
Marshall Faulk, I mean, did you ever see
the kid watching him and now you're
playing golf with him and it's just kind
of like he's pretty good at that, too.
Yeah, I mean, this guy he's a Hall of
Famer for a reason. I mean, it feels
like anything that he picks up, he gets
pretty good at it. He was the player of
the day today. The way he was hitting
the ball was just throwing darts. Yeah,
really really good player.
How do you feel about the draft?
Obviously, I know you you haven't been
here maybe as long as some of the guys,
but you are one of the people who was
brought here to kind of change this
culture and bring this program back. Do
you get excited about the draft and
knowing at 8 you may get a real impact
player? Yeah, absolutely. Absolutely.
The draft is so fun because, you know,
every guy that's in the locker room, you
know, it kind of takes you back to your
own draft experience and um, when the
guys get [clears throat] in and you
know, it's it's like it's like having
kids that when your kids go through
something, you get to relive it
>> with them. So, it's that same thing with
these young guys that come in, you get
to take money and we pour into them. Um,
whatever we get, we're going to bring
them into the culture, teach them how we
do things, teach them how to be
professional and uh, expect some big
plays out of them. So, excited about
that for them, excited about um, all the
momentum that we have going into this
season. We finished on the upswing last
year and we're just going to, you know,
continue that energy and momentum.
Montee Ball
wasn't at LSU long. Did you ever get a
chance to meet him or or Who was he at
LSU? Uh, Montee Ball. He he was only
there for the one year, so I didn't know
if you ever had a chance to meet him or
come across him. He's obviously one of
those guys that's that's in the cloud of
potential in the top 10 picks. Yeah,
yeah, no, I haven't had a chance to talk
with him, but the football community as
players, coaches, whatever, says it's a
fraternity for a reason.
Um, even though I haven't talked to him
directly, I'm sure we know a ton of
mutual people, especially all the LSU
connections
um, that run deep. Do you know Do you
know Sorry, to interrupt. Do you know a
lot about Caleb Downs at all? And um,
you know, if so, what would that mean to
you to be able to kind of potentially
play next to a guy like that if you
know, he ends up selecting him at 8? Guy
guy is an absolute stud. Talented
player, can put him anywhere on the
field.
Um, a lot of similar traits to uh, the
guy in Baltimore that just come as
impact player, can maybe play some
nickel, can play deep safety, play zone,
has shown some blitzing ability. Um,
talented player, wherever he goes and
plays, um, he's going to be a special
kid and if we pull him here, we'll be
lucky to have him. I hate to keep asking
about the draft.
How do you guys kind of build off of
what you did last year in close last
year and just start strong
Yeah, you know, it's about taking that
momentum with us, you know, like last
year was all about setting the
foundation, learning who we were from
the get-go as a team. There's a ton of
new faces and Coach Kelly was very
intentional about creating a culture,
creating an identity of who we are and
how we do things and now we don't have
to spend as much time building it. We
get to just run with it. We get to take
what we've already done, build on top of
it, continue to go.
Um, so, a lot of good things, there's a
lot of positive energy in the building.
It felt like the first day of school
yesterday. Everybody coming back in, um,
excited to get to to get to work and
we're just going to keep on with
building. Any draft plans for you? Just
kind of hang out, watch it? Any draft
plans?
>> Yeah, no, nothing special. Just kind of
enjoy it like everybody else. I turn
into a fan like everybody else and get
to see what we get. Do you I hate to ask
you about so many players, but I know
Bailey started at Stanford. Did you meet
him because of Stanford connections
before he went to Texas Tech at all?
Just kind of any thoughts on a guy who's
considered a top edge rusher?
Yeah, you know what? Um, again, like
he'll have the chance to play with Carl
Granderson, Chase Young.
Um, we grab that guy and like the the
amount of
knowledge that these guys going to be
able to pour into him,
um,
is going to be able to help him
tremendously. You know, having edge
playing edge in this defense is
particular fun particularly fun uh,
because you're going to have a whole lot
of time, a whole lot of opportunities
uh, to be able to get one-on-one rushes
against the quarterback uh, against the
tackle to get to the quarterback. So,
um, man, you know what? Like the process
is just go through the process, enjoy
it. Whoever we get is going to be a
big-time player for us and we're going
to pour into him and expect a lot from
him.